instagrok.com 2016-12-24

# Privacy Policy | instaGrok.com

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting this website (the "Site"), made available to you by instaGrok inc. ("instaGrok"). instaGrok is committed to protecting your privacy. We've developed this Privacy Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose, and make use of personal information that you provide to us on this Site. By using the Site and voluntarily providing personal information in connection with your registration or use, you are consenting to our use of the information you provide as described in this Privacy Policy.

### The Information We Collect

#### Required Personal Information

The site can be used without creating an account. Certain features, however, require registration. If you register as a General user or as a Teacher/Librarian, you will be asked to provide your email address, a user ID of your choosing, and a password. If a payment is necessary, you will be asked to provide credit card or billing information. If you register as a student, you will be asked to provide a user ID of your choosing and a password. Teachers and Students are asked to associate their accounts with specific classes.

If you are accessing instaGrok through another website that offers single-sign-on to multiple applications, that other service's privacy policy may override instaGrok's.

#### Other Collected Information

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit the Site, such as the type of browser and operating system you are using, the IP address you are using to connect to the Site, and the name of your Internet service provider. This type of information helps us ensure consistent delivery of the Site and improve our services.

We also collect information on how you use the Site, such as what topics users have researched.

### Cookies

Like most major websites, we may use "cookies" to store information during your use of our Site. Cookies are small pieces of code that are stored in a designated file on your computer. They do not provide us with any personally identifiable information and cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

We use cookies as a convenience feature to save you time, and to help us both understand how our Site is used and improve the Site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages or recall your specific information on subsequent visits (for example, to recognize you by name when you return to the Site). If you would prefer not to receive any cookies, most browsers can be set to refuse cookies or to alert you when one is being sent. It is possible, however, that some portions of this Site may not function properly if the cookies are disabled.

Third parties such as advertisers may add a cookie to help analyze web traffic or to determine targeted advertisements based on your preferences and your visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. To opt out of Google's use of cookies, please visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

### Updating Or Removing Your Personal Information

You may update or remove yourself from our database by contacting us:

  * (720) 583-4765

### How We Use Your Personal Information

We will use the personal information you provide in connection with your use of the Site. If we need to contact you, we may do so using your email address. Information we collect about how you use the Site--such as what topics you have researched--will be presented to you as your research history. We may also use it (in a way that is not personally identifiable) to improve our service and add new features.

Please be aware that any information that you disclose on the site--for instance, when customizing your Grok or writing in your journal--may be accessible to other users. instaGrok cannot take any responsibility for such collection or disclosure.

### How We Share Your Personal Information

instaGrok is not in the business of selling the information you provide to us to any other party. We will not share the personal information you provide except (a) if it is for the purpose(s) you provided it; (b) with your consent; (c) as may be required by law or as we think necessary to protect our company or others from injury; or (d) with vendors who provide services to us, such as hosting services, tech support, database managers, and credit card processors.

### Links To Other Sites

This Privacy Policy applies only to our Site. Our Site may provide links to--or embed media from--other websites that are not under our control. These other sites do not follow our privacy policies and procedures, and may place their own cookies on your computer. You should review the privacy policies on those sites to understand how they will protect any personal information you provide.

### Security Of The Information You Provide

We believe we have taken reasonable steps to protect the information you provide us from loss or theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification.

### International Users

If you are visiting our Site from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States and all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using this Site, you authorize the export of personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us. This policy and our legal obligations are subject to the laws of the State of California and the USA, regardless of the location of any user. Any claims or complaints must be filed in the USA in the State of California.

### Changes To This Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of September 30, 2013. Since our policy may change periodically, without notice, please check back here from time to time to review our current Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site after the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy means you accept such changes.

### How To Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, need to contact us about the information you've provided, or want to terminate your registration, you may reach us using any of these methods:

  * (720) 583-4765
